export const QuestionData = [
    {
        question: "question 1",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 2                                 //note that the index is starting from 1.
    },
    {
        question: "question 2",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "question 3",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "question 4",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "question 5",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "question 6",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "question 7",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "question 8",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "question 9",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "question 10",
        options:[ "A", "B", "C", "D"],
        answer: 3
    }
];
